<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
	<string name="app_name">Movie Catalogue</string>
	<string name="change_language_settings">Change Language Settings</string>
	<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
	<string name="name_movies">Catalog Movie</string>
	<string name="judul_film">Movie</string>
	<string name="judul_tv">TV Show</string>

	<string-array name="data_name">
		<item>A Star</item>
		<item>Aquaman</item>
		<item>Avenger Infinity War</item>
		<item>The BirdBox</item>
		<item>Bohemian</item>
		<item>Bumblebee</item>
		<item>The Creed</item>
		<item>Deadpool</item>
		<item>Dragon</item>
		<item>Dragon Ball</item>
		<item>Venom</item>
		<item>The Mule</item>
		<item>Spiderman</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="data_description">
		<item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers — and falls in love with — struggling artist Ally. She has just
			about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight. But even
			as Allys career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an
			ongoing battle with his own internal demons.
		</item>
		<item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the
			power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people
			and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orms half-human, half-Atlantean brother and
			true heir to the throne.
		</item>
		<item>During World War II, Steve Rogers is a sickly man from Brooklyn whos transformed into super-soldier
			Captain America to aid in the war effort. Rogers must stop the Red Skull – Adolf Hitlers ruthless head of
			weaponry, and the leader of an organization that intends to use a mysterious device of untold powers for
			world domination.
		</item>
		<item>Pony and Birdboy tells a story of seven-year-old girl Pony, who doesn’t want to go to school, and
			big-mouthed Birdboy who has solution to all possible problems. Humoristic family-film Pony and Birdboy is
			partly based on Veera Salmi’s popular children’s book The Book of Pony and Birdboy, which rich humor and
			anarchist hustle have brought the book as a favorite of children.
		</item>
		<item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the
			music world by storm when they form the rock n roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics.
			When Mercurys increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest
			challenge yet – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.
		</item>
		<item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town.
			Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee,
			battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.
		</item>
		<item>The former World Heavyweight Champion Rocky Balboa serves as a trainer and mentor to Adonis Johnson, the
			son of his late friend and former rival Apollo Creed.
		</item>
		<item>Deadpool tells the origin story of former Special Forces operative turned mercenary Wade Wilson, who after
			being subjected to a rogue experiment that leaves him with accelerated healing powers, adopts the alter ego
			Deadpool. Armed with his new abilities and a dark, twisted sense of humor, Deadpool hunts down the man who
			nearly destroyed his life.
		</item>
		<item>For years, old wood carver Mr. Meacham has delighted local children with his tales of the fierce dragon
			that resides deep in the woods of the Pacific Northwest. To his daughter, Grace, who works as a forest
			ranger, these stories are little more than tall tales until she meets Pete, a mysterious 10-year-old with no
			family and no home who claims to live in the woods with a giant, green dragon named Elliott. And from Petes
			descriptions, Elliott seems remarkably similar to the dragon from Mr. Meachams stories. With the help of
			Natalie, an 11-year-old girl whose father Jack owns the local lumber mill, Grace sets out to determine where
			Pete came from, where he belongs, and the truth about this dragon.
		</item>
		<item>The young warrior Son Goku sets out on a quest, racing against time and the vengeful King Piccolo, to
			collect a set of seven magical orbs that will grant their wielder unlimited power.
		</item>
		<item>Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the
			host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to
			protect the world from a shadowy organization looking for a symbiote of their own.
		</item>
		<item>Earl Stone, a man in his 80s, is broke, alone, and facing foreclosure of his business when he is offered a
			job that simply requires him to drive. Easy enough, but, unbeknownst to Earl, he’s just signed on as a drug
			courier for a Mexican cartel. He does so well that his cargo increases exponentially, and Earl hit the radar
			of hardcharging DEA agent Colin Bates.
		</item>
		<item>Peter Parker and his friends go on a summer trip to Europe. However, they will hardly be able to rest -
			Peter will have to agree to help Nick Fury uncover the mystery of creatures that cause natural disasters and
			destruction throughout the continent.
		</item>
	</string-array>
	<array name="data_photo">
		<item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_themule</item>
		<item>@drawable/poster_spiderman</item>
	</array>
	<string-array name="data_tv">
		<item>The Sopranos</item>
		<item>Game of Thrones</item>
		<item>The Wire</item>
		<item>Dexter</item>
		<item>Breaking Bad</item>
		<item>The walking Dead</item>
		<item>Broadwalk Empire</item>
		<item>Rome</item>
		<item>Mad Man</item>
		<item>Son of Anarchy</item>
		<item>The west wing</item>
		<item>Weeds</item>
		<item>Lost</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="data_desctv">
		<item>New Jersey mob boss Tony Soprano deals with personal and professional issues in his home and business life
			that affect his mental state, leading him to seek professional psychiatric counseling.
		</item>
		<item>Nine noble families fight for control over the mythical lands of Westeros, while an ancient enemy returns
			after being dormant for thousands of years.
		</item>
		<item>The Baltimore drug scene, as seen through the eyes of drug dealers and law enforcement.</item>
		<item>By day, mild-mannered Dexter is a blood-spatter analyst for the Miami police. But at night, he is a serial
			killer who only targets other murderers.
		</item>
		<item>A high school chemistry teacher diagnosed with inoperable lung cancer turns to manufacturing and selling
			methamphetamine in order to secure his familys future.
		</item>
		<item>Sheriff Deputy Rick Grimes wakes up from a coma to learn the world is in ruins, and must lead a group of
			survivors to stay alive.
		</item>
		<item>An Atlantic City politician plays both sides of the law by conspiring with gangsters during the
			Prohibition era.
		</item>
		<item>A down-to-earth account of the lives of both illustrious and ordinary Romans set in the last days of the
			Roman Republic.
		</item>
		<item>A drama about one of New Yorks most prestigious ad agencies at the beginning of the 1960s, focusing on
			one of the firms most mysterious but extremely talented ad executives, Donald Draper.
		</item>
		<item>A biker struggles to balance being a father and being involved in an outlaw motorcycle club.</item>
		<item>Inside the lives of staffers in the West Wing of the White House.</item>
		<item>When a suburban mother turns to dealing marijuana in order to maintain her privileged lifestyle after her
			husband dies, she finds out just how addicted her entire neighborhood already is.
		</item>
		<item>The survivors of a plane crash are forced to work together in order to survive on a seemingly deserted
			tropical island.
		</item>
	</string-array>
	<array name="data_phototv">
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGJjYzhjYTYtMDBjYy00OWU1LTg5OTYtNmYwOTZmZjE3ZDdhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTAyODkwOQ@@._V1_UY209_CR3,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA5NzA5NjMwNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjg2OTk2NzM@._V1_UY209_CR0,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjc1NzYwODEyMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTcxMzU1MQ@@._V1_UY209_CR7,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTM5MjkwMTI0MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODQwMTc0OQ@@._V1_UY209_CR7,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjhiMzgxZTctNDc1Ni00OTIxLTlhMTYtZTA3ZWFkODRkNmE2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzkwMjQ5NzM@._V1_UY209_CR5,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWY4ODJiZjMtNWMxYi00ZmM5LWIwZmQtZWY0MjJmZGU5MjcxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkxNjUyNQ@@._V1_UY209_CR0,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYTYxNzc5ZmYtODcyNi00ZWUwLWExNWUtY2Y0YTlhZDBlMGU1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzQ1ODk3MTQ@._V1_UY209_CR2,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTM4NjBkMWEtZDA4My00MzA0LWI0ZWMtNzUwYWVhOThiMTgwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTAyODkwOQ@@._V1_UY209_CR9,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMwNzk5Nzg2OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjg1OTk1NDE@._V1_UY209_CR1,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTEyODg2NzkwMDBeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDQwODI3MzIx._V1_UY209_CR0,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjk3ZWE3ZDctN2Q1YS00NzNhLWFjNmYtZTkwYWQxZmQ3NzM3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTE1NjY5Mg@@._V1_UX140_CR0,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY1MTg1MTcxNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTI4ODUzMQ@@._V1_UY209_CR14,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
		<item>
			"https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzhlY2E5NDUtYjJjYy00ODg3LWFkZWQtYTVmMzU4ZWZmOWJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_UX140_CR0,0,140,209_AL_.jpg"
		</item>
	</array>

	<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
	<string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
	<string name="title_activity_detail">DetailActivity</string>
</resources>
